https://www.marinersmuseum.org/terms-privacy/

Terms & Privacy - The Mariners' Museum and Park
100 Museum Dr Newport News, VA23606 Museum: ClosedPark and Noland Trail: Open
MenuVisitPlan Your DayAccessibilityDirections & ParkingHours & AdmissionExplorers TheaterFood & ShoppingPark & TrailUpcoming EventsEvents CalendarMaritime MondaysCivil War DiscussionsFriendly HoursGuided Park ToursVirtual ProgrammingGroupsAbout Group ToursPlan Your VisitDining OptionsBook Your ReservationTourism & Group ContactsWho We AreAbout UsGovernancePress ReleasesFinancialsEmploymentInternshipsContact Us CloseExploreCurrent ExhibitionsAge of ExplorationA Head of Its TimeCrabtree GalleryDefending the SeasInternational Small Craft CenterSeizing the Moment: The Evolution of Action PhotographyShip Model GallerySpeed and Innovation in the America’s CupThe Nelson TouchToys AhoyUSS Monitor CenterCollectionsCollections HighlightsFAQCatalogsSearch all CatalogsRights and ReproductionsLibraryAboutContact UsPlans & DrawingsSpecial CollectionsPhotography CollectionChris-CraftLibrary GalleryMariners’ BlogHomeCollectionsLibrary & ArchivesUSS Monitor CenterPhotographyStaff VoicesCivil War90th Birthday CloseLearnSchools & Youth GroupsEducation ProgramsVirtual Education ProgramsSummer ProgramsHomeschool ProgramsBook a ProgramScoutsOnline LearningChanging World ViewsNewport News in World War IThe Ages of ExplorationInt’l Small Craft CenterChesapeake BayAfrican Americans & the BayBirth of the NavyBattle of the AtlanticMessage in a BottleWomen & the SeaFamilies & ChildrenMuseum Fun at HomeMaritime MondaysAdult LearnersLecturesSpeakers BureauVideo Conferencing CloseGive & JoinSupport the MuseumMembershipCorporate SupportVolunteer CloseRentalsInformationGeneral InfoPhoto AlbumFAQRequest a TourLocations & RatesApproved CaterersMuseum Rental Packages Close
Become aMember!
Become aMember!
Terms & PrivacyThis policy was last modified on December 6, 2018.This Website (“Site”) is owned and operated by The Mariners’ Museum (“We” / “Us” / “Our”), 100 Museum Drive, Newport News, VA 23606. The Site is for private, non-commercial, informational, and entertainment purposes only.We provide the content on this Site, in support of Our mission to “connect people to the world’s waters, because through the waters—through our shared maritime heritage—we are connected to one another.”These Terms & Conditions and Privacy Policies are enforced in accordance with the laws of the Commonwealth of Virginia and the United States of America. Terms & Conditions Policy Privacy Policy Policy Contact Site AttributionTerms & Conditions PolicyAbout the TermsBy using this Site, you the visitor (“You” / “Your”) must accept and agree to abide by the following terms. We reserve the right to update or modify these Terms & Conditions at any time without prior notice. If You do not agree to these Terms & Conditions and the Privacy Policy, please do not access, use, or participate on this Site. We may at any time revise these Terms & Conditions by updating this page. You are bound by any such revisions and should therefore periodically visit this page to review the then-current Terms & Conditions.If We decide to change these Terms & Conditions, We will post those changes on this page and update the modification date at the top of this page.Copyrights and Intellectual PropertyWe are the owner of the compilation of content that is posted on this Site, which consists of text, images, audio, video, databases, design, codes, and software (“Content”). All intellectual property rights (registered and unregistered), including copyright, design, patents, photographs, illustrations, software and trademarks in and on this Site shall remain vested with Us or Our licensors.You may make fair use of Our content as defined by copyright law of the United States of America. Information on United States copyright fair use law is available from the United States Copyright Office (see http://www.copyright.gov/fls/fl102.html). Please note, You are responsible for determining whether Your use is fair and for responding to any claims that may arise from Your use. If You use copies of this Site’s text and/or images for purposes in excess of “fair use” as defined by the copyright law, You may be liable for copyright infringement.The Mariners’ Museum permits the nonexclusive use of digital and print reproductions of its collection and archival materials according to applicable rights and restrictions. Individuals or organizations that would like to obtain a reproduction must first obtain permission from The Mariners’ Museum Digital Services department using instructions here.For information about use of images and their copyrights, restrictions, and proper citation, see our “Rights and Reproductions” page.External LinksThis Site may contain links to other sites. These linked sites are outside of Our control, and as such, We do not accept responsibility or liability for their content, materials, products or services, or warrant the accuracy or security of the linked sites. If You visit a linked site, You do so entirely at Your own risk. Our inclusion of linked sites does not imply any endorsement of the material on them or any association with their owners or operators. Linked sites may contain advertisements—these advertisements are not recommendations or endorsements by Us and We are not responsible for the products or services being advertised.Intellectual property rights of othersWe respect the intellectual property rights of others and prohibit materials that violate another party’s intellectual property rights. If You believe any material on this Site infringes upon a copyright, please send a written notification of such infringement to Our Webmaster by taking the following steps:Identify the content and URL that contains the material You claim infringes Your copyright. Please word this similar to the following: “The picture of the ____ (or text) at the following URL infringes on my copyright: http://…”State that You believe “in good faith” that the material You identify as copyrighted is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent, or the law.State that the information contained in Your copyright notice “is accurate to the best of my knowledge”, and that You attest under the penalty of perjury that You are the copyright owner or that You are authorized to act on the copyright owner’s behalf.Include Your name, mailing address, telephone number, and email address. Forward these details to the address listed on the Policy Contact tab.We will attempt to contact the source of the allegedly infringing material and may remove any content that is the subject of a notice under this clause within a reasonable time. We reserve the right to take any further steps We deem necessary to further investigate such content.As-is disclaimerWithout limiting the foregoing, all materials on this Site are provided “AS IS” WITHOUT A WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EITHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR USE, AND/OR NON-INFRINGEMENT. We assume no responsibility, and shall not be liable for, any damages to or viruses that may infect Your computer equipment or other property as a result of Your use of this Site or Your downloading of any materials from this Site.Privacy PolicyWe are committed to protecting the privacy of Our online visitors, customers, members, donors, patrons, and friends.When this Privacy Policy references the term “personally identifiable information” or “personal information,” We mean information that identifies a particular individual, such as Your full name, street address, telephone number, or email address. When other information, such as a hobby or demographic-identifier, is associated with personal information, it also becomes personally identifiable information for the purposes of this Privacy Policy.We do not collect personally identifiable information about individuals, such as names and postal or email addresses, unless the individual knowingly provides it.This online Privacy Policy applies only to information collected through our Websites (“Sites”) and not to information collected offline.If We decide to change Our Privacy Policy, We will post those changes on this page and update the modification date at the top of this page.What information do We collect?Listed below are the types of information collected on all Sites We own and operate: Information Collected From All VisitorsVisitors to this Site who have JavaScript enabled are tracked using the following services:Google Analytics and Google Analytics Advertising FeaturesOur Google Analytics implementation collects the following types of information from users:Type of user agent (Web browser) used, software manufacture and version number.Type of operating system and Web browserScreen colors (color processing ability of the users screen)JavaScript supportFlash versionScreen resolutionNetwork location and IP address:Can include country, city, state, region, county, or any other geographic data.HostnameBandwidth (internet connection speed)Time of visitPages visitedTime spent on each page of the SiteReferring site statistics:The site (URI) the user came through in order to arrive at this Site (example: clicking on a hyperlink from Google.com that took the user to this Site)Search engine query used (example: typing in a phrase into a search engine like Google.com, and clicking on a link from that search engine)Our Google Analytics Advertising Features implementation includes Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting, which collects the following types of information from Our users:AgeGenderLifestyle interestsProduct-purchase interestsYou can can opt-out of Our Google Analytics Advertising Features using the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on.Facebook PixelOur Facebook Pixel implementation helps us measure the return on investment of Our Facebook Ads by reporting on the actions people take after viewing those ads. We create pixels that track conversions, add them to the pages of Our websites where the conversions will happen, and then track these conversions back to ads they are running on Facebook.No personal information is contained in or collected as a result of using these pixels.You can opt-out of the collection of your data by Facebook Pixel or to the use of your data for the purpose of displaying Facebook ads by changing your Facebook ad preferences.We use tracking data primarily to optimize Our Sites for Our visitors. We also use this data for internal reporting, identifying Our audiences, for marketing purposes, and for writing fundraising proposals.This data DOES NOT include any personalized identification information such as:NamesPhone NumbersEmail AddressesLocation or Mailing AddressesSocial Security NumbersBank Account NumbersCredit Card Information Information Collected from All Users Who Register on Our WebsitesOnline Purchases and DonationsYou may use Our Sites without registering or submitting any personally identifiable information. However, when You purchase a product, make a donation, or buy a membership online from Us, You may be asked to provide such information that may include a user name and password, Your name, membership number, billing and shipping addresses, telephone number, fax number if You have one, email address, and credit card information to process Your transaction. Your information will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without Your express consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.We store and use order information as follows:Order information: We will retain Your order information, as listed above, for Our records, so We can track Your order and facilitate customer service.Credit card information: We will use Your credit card information only as needed to process Your transaction or issue a refund if necessary. Following best PCI compliance practices, We never store Your credit card information on Our servers. Online credit card purchases are processed by either Blackbaud Merchant Services, operated by Blackbaud, or Authorize.Net. Both Blackbaud and Authorize.Net have validated compliance with the Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI DSS), as required by American Express, Visa USA, MasterCard International, Discover, JCB and Diners Club. Additionally, Blackbaud has validated compliance with the Payment Application Data Security Standard (PA DSS).Email addresses: The email addresses You provide for order processing, may be used to send You information and updates pertaining to Your order, in addition to receiving occasional Mariners’ Museum news, updates, related product or service information, etc. We include an unsubscribe link at the bottom of each email so you can unsubscribe at any time.Employment, Volunteer, and Internship ApplicationsPersonal applicant information and uploaded documents (e.g., résumé, cover letter, transcripts, etc.) submitted via online application forms are securely transmitted via a 256-bit SSL encrypted connection between Your browser and either a server operated by ATS OnDemand for employment applications or by Our Gravity Forms server for volunteer and internship applications. ATS OnDemand is an online application tracking service We use for storing and managing employment applications. Our staff uses submitted employment, volunteer, and internship applications and uploaded documents for selecting qualified applicants for interview. We retain applications and uploaded documents for one year after the application date. No applications or uploaded documents are kept in a “résumé pool” for future consideration.Newsletters and Website EmailsWe may offer newsletters to share information with You about the Site, about The Mariners’ Museum, and about Our partners and affiliates. You may sign up to receive a newsletter either by registering for a particular newsletter or in conjunction with a special feature or membership for which You have registered on the Website. You do have to provide Us with personal information when You sign up for a newsletter. We include an unsubscribe link at the bottom of each newsletter email so you can unsubscribe at any time.Surveys and FormsWe post online surveys and forms to solicit comments, opinions, and requests from our audiences. Information submitted via Our online surveys and forms is securely transmitted via a 128-bit SSL encrypted connection between Your browser and a Google server. Survey and form responses are automatically recorded into Google Apps Spreadsheets stored on secure Google servers. We may choose to export those spreadsheets for offline storage, printing, or reporting when necessary.Do We use cookies?Yes. Cookies are small files of information that are stored on Your computer’s hard drive by Your browser that enables the Site’s or service provider’s systems to recognize Your browser and capture and remember certain information. Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but You can change the preferences of Your browser so it does not accept them. Additionally, you might consider using the online NAI Consumer Opt Out tool to opt-out from receiving interest-based digital advertising.The cookies We use do not contain any personally identifiable information. We use cookies to help Us remember and process the items in Your shopping cart and compile aggregate data about Site traffic and Site interaction so that We can offer better Site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist Us in better understanding Our Site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on Our behalf except to help Us operate and improve Our organization.To make purchases online from Us, We recommend You accept cookies.Do We disclose any information to outside parties?We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties Your personally identifiable information. We may release Your information when We believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce Our Site policies, or protect ours or others’ rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for research, marketing, advertising, or other uses.California Online Privacy Protection Act (CalOPPA) ComplianceWe value Your privacy and have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute Your personal information to outside parties without Your consent.Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) ComplianceWe do not solicit or collect any personally identifiable information from anyone under 13 years of age. Thus, We are not required to comply with the Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act. Some of Our Sites and products are directed to children under 13, but no personally identifiable information is solicited or collected.Policy ContactSend Your questions, comments, or concerns about Our Privacy & Terms Policy or any other aspect of Our Sites to:The Mariners’ Museum & Park Attn: Webmaster 100 Museum Drive Newport News, VA 23606 USAEmail: webmaster@MarinersMuseum.org Tel: (757) 952-0431 Fax: (757) 591-7319Site AttributionThe following parties are responsible for publishing or producing content displayed on or used by this Site or Us in the course of business. Attribution is listed here per acceptance and agreement of terms with these parties.SimpleMaps.comUnited States Cities Database at https://simplemaps.com/data/us-citiesUS Zip Codes Database at https://simplemaps.com/data/us-zipsDark Sky Weather APIPowered by Dark Sky at https://darksky.net/poweredby/
Contact Info
The Mariners’ Museum and Park 100 Museum Dr, Newport News, VA 23606
Museum  (757) 596-2222 Security  (757) 591-7777 After Hours Security  (757) 254-2144
Send us a message© 1995 – 2020 The Mariners’ Museum and Park. All Rights Reserved. The Mariners’ Museum is a U.S. 501(c)(3) non-profit organization.Support Us
Donate Now Become a MemberStay Connected
Subscribe here to get our news and events sent to your inbox!
Terms & PrivacyDonor PrivacyEmploymentAbout UsContact UsDonation and Prize Request
×
×
×
×
×
×
×
×
×
E-newsletters Sign-up
Ahoy! Thank you for signing up for our e-newsletters. Please select any specific interests you may have in the options below. We are thrilled to have you aboard and look forward to seeing you in the Museum soon.Email Address
First Name Last Name Interests
Family Fun
Education Events
Food and Beverage Events
Park and Noland Trail
Lecture Series
Donation Leave this field empty if you're human:
×
